<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TextView</string>

    <string name="yearly_horoscope">Aries \n\n Sometimes, Aries natives get highly motivated and strong-opinionated, which might get them into problems easily. However, sometimes the same dominant factor can help them win some extremely hard battles in their lives. The Aries yearly horoscope 2023 predicts that even though you would be on your impulses, the year will be a strong one for you. Sometimes, it would add to your charm, while sometimes, it might challenge you to become better in life. Planetary support would be there with you. But, the year would make you more prepared for the upcoming hurdles and situations in your life. Hard times are to test you. Battling the ups and the downs will be too many. But you are Aries, and you know how to deal with the emotional as well as physical ups and downs. However, beware of some issues that may come with Rahu in the third quarter. You can rely on Jupiter as it would be an aid to your life all through the year. Make some plans on doing things with the abundance that will come with the change of planetary motions in the second half of 2023 for Aries men and women. Up for interesting beginnings and a roller coaster ride on the parallel? Well, Aries hit the jam in the year your way.\n \n
     Taurus \n\n Taurus people are pros at being focused in their lives. But the Taurus yearly horoscope 2023 wants you to make some changes— the good ones. In order to follow your dreams and give your best shot at everything, you may have to interfere with your regular life. The predictions do not say that the year will make you struggle. However, it will definitely make you better by placing you in hard situations where your decisions would be the king. With some clashes with people around you, things might look a little twisted. But worry not, Taurus buddies, as your ruling planet Venus, will be a blessing to your personal as well as professional life. However, on the other hand, Rahu could be a little troublesome for all areas of your life. It would trick you into doing things that can harm the things you built all this while. But worry not, as Ketu is there to save you from difficult challenges. Safeguarding yourself from the ups and downs will be something the New Year 2023 will be expecting from you and thus, a year of learning is here for you, with the support and attentiveness of the planets. \n\n
     Gemini \n\n Duality runs in your character. So, how about reshaping yourself to embrace the best in the year? The Gemini yearly horoscope 2023 predicts that head-on situations can occur in front of you, where you purposely have to keep your duality aside and act patiently to solve the situation. The year will be prosperous for you. But, for the same to happen, you shall get everything into alignment. Moreover, you need to figure out what is the requirement of the time. People around you are definitely your friends but do not rely too much on them, as planet Saturn will soon make you realise that you are better on your own and capable of doing everything on your own. Planet Mars and Venus will be helpful and work in your favor. So, even if your dual personality takes you in two different directions, worry not, as the planetary transits 2023 are there to help you, be you understand what is right and what is wrong, and make you successful in many areas of your life. So Gemini natives, work on healthy practices regularly—health-wise, professionally, and financially, and make some necessary modifications with a little bit of your personality touch, and 2023 will become your dream year.\n\n
     Cancer \n\n We can see Cancer natives crawling into their comfort zone as soon as they get the opportunity. But the Cancer yearly horoscope 2023 says it wont be the thing to do this year. Planets got your back! So, give your passions and plans the best shot you got. With the right strike on life and appropriate enthusiasm and energy, you will succeed even on the not-so-favorable days of the year. Ahead, For the Cancer natives, the year indicates a conflict in your head— be emotional and say it all or show everybody your practical side and be in your shoes and observe. To help you decide, Jupiter will be there. Be it your professional life or your personal life, the planet will be helpful. However, mind that Saturn is there too and will slow you down to let you understand life differently. Also, Ketu will be in action too, which will become a mini passage towards success in most of the years of your life. But, for the same to happen, all you need is a pinch of advice (in some areas of your life) and total faith in yourself, and good results will be there in your life in no time.\n\n
     Leo \n\n For the brave Leo natives, nothing in life is hard. Even though the year might throw some challenges in your path, you will do pretty great. The Leo yearly horoscope 2023 predictions say that contentment would be the best for you in the year. But your thirst to be the best and have the best will make you put in the most appropriate efforts you can. The planets do demand this from you. But, on the other hand, they also would want you to evaluate before taking everything on your dignity and pride. So, right from the first month, believe in the good things. Cherish the moments you have instead of worrying about what is not there with you. Around the third quarter, when planet Jupiter will be in action, things will definitely improve for good. Venus will be there too to bring some changes and positivity to your professional life. But, hold yourself back, Leos, as Saturn and Rahu would be there to give you hurdles and hindrances from time to time. Thus, beware of the challenges that may be there in your life, especially, health-wise, as the New Year could be a little hard on you in terms of well-being.\n\n
     Virgo \n\n You are one of the most sane-headed folks on the zodiac table. But even you are not perfect. Right? The Virgo yearly horoscope 2023 comes with a tiny alert sign for you— avoid rushing to conclusions! There are all kinds of possibilities for the natives in the year. Thus, this little advice would save you days and weeks in the year and help you to improve whatever was left in the last year. Mars and Mercury are here with ample good opportunities right in the first half of the year, and with their blessings, you will do things that were unplanned but possible, confused? Well, don’t be. Virgo natives are likely to have a taste of their own efforts. So, even if things might come to you suddenly, consider them a result of your past deeds and works. Stay alert around the end, as Ketu will be in action. Highs and lows because of this planetary transit 2023, there are possibilities of changes in the finances and relations you possess. Facing hurdles and good times, you shall enjoy a mini roller-coaster ride. But, definitely, you are way off from falling into a pit, so rejoice and cherish whatever you can in 2023.\n\n
     Libra \n\n We all know that balance is the key to your calmness. And the Libra yearly horoscope 2023 strongly indicates the same. However, introspection, understanding the developments, and making changes according to the time would be something you will need. Planetary transits will favour you to quite an extent and bring satisfaction to your life. Still, remember that not everything that is correct will work for you. Where, on one side, some planets would try to shake the equilibrium you love, others will help you attain it back again. Right from the first quarter of 2023, you would have to be in action. Libra natives must mind the point that although Saturn is here to test you for things, Rahu is to trick you in situations, you have to search for the silver lining in everything. For some period of time, you may require the help of others. Avoid being egoistic and must seek the required help. Soon, it will be your door to satisfaction in the year 2023 as luck, opportunities, and great things are waiting for you in the year; only you have to be utterly clear and positive about the things you are planning or looking out for.\n\n
     Scorpio \n\n Scorpio natives do not interact much. As much as they love to be on their own, the Scorpio yearly horoscope 2023 would help them in the same. In fact, the same habit can be productive for you. However, on the other hand, a little modification is all you will need to attract the happy-go-lucky times in your life. Planet Jupiter transit in 2023 will be a great chance for you to clarify some things in your mind. However, on the other hand, Saturn transit will come as an alert to certain areas of your life. This combination of events will surely change your perception in multiple ways. Also, it would break some beliefs you had about life and some people in it. Sounds like an eye-opening year? Well, it is. Scorpio natives will see things fall into the right place in the second half of the year when much of the toxicity will be gone from your life. Moreover, if you have a New Year resolution list; well, go for the implementation. On the contrary, keep the process slow and steady because the planetary transits would only let you be in alignment with your life if you adopt patience and perseverance.\n\n
     Sagittarius \n\n By all means, you can call this a favourable year. The Sagittarius yearly horoscope 2023 marks a time for exploration and understanding. Not only will you get the planets blessings, but also make some great accomplishments. When Venus and Jupiter will be present helping you together, things shall seem easy and nice. However, the Ketu transit 2023 would be a stopper to many things in your life. On one hand, it would save you from the wrong company, and on the other hand, it will indicate the path you must pick in its own way. Look for signs and be yourself. Also, Sagittarius natives, take a big sigh if you are looking for the right one in your head and heart, as the horoscope indicates some possibilities. But don’t be hasty, avoid being overwhelmed, and be who you actually are, as for the Sagittarius natives, on an overall basis, 2023 would be the Perfect year! Also, don’t fly too high if repetitively things work your way, as some twists could be there too, pushing you to make amendments and changes to get a clear viewpoint on life and its ways. Therefore, a miniature warning— stay away from risky ways to have a great life.\n\n
     Capricorn \n\n Hurdles would come and go, but Capricorns won’t give up! And that should stay your attitude in 2023. Strongly, standing on your ethics and ways of living life, you would do pretty well, as per the Capricorn yearly horoscope 2023. Your policies will not only get you success but also help you achieve all the leftover plans of the previous year. You need to express yourself right and manage all the areas of your life with a correct attitude and mindfulness. While your finances will be great, you may face troubles regarding your health. Planet Saturn will be there to delay some events. However, planet Jupiter will save you from multiple adversities. Right from the first quarter, your attitude will be positive about everything that shall come your way this year. Be it your love life or your married one, Capricorn natives are likely to enjoy their time with their partners from time to time. But, for the same to happen, you will need to follow a queue of thoughts. However, on the other hand, remember not to run into any shortcuts as that would surely drag you to the other side of the road in no time. So, stick to your nobility and follow what you are best at— Being Yourself!\n\n
     Aquarius \n\n Just like your symbol, you bear too much to say out loud. But, the Aquarius yearly horoscope 2023 will share some days and events with you wherein you can enjoy some me-time and work on yourself to achieve better things in the year ahead. Moreover, the year would be great for you if you are constantly putting in all your efforts in the right places. On the contrary, remember not to ignore any warnings that hold you back from performing something. Right things will come with Sun and Mars, especially in your personal life. The Mars transit 2023 will also fix things that were running off-track from the previous year. Influence of planets Rahu and Ketu would be there too on your horoscope, but Aquarius natives, you need to show the situations your best and impeccable side. Even if the situation looks hard, stick to the right things, and soon around the third quarter, the missing piece of your puzzle will be right in front of your eyes. Stay a little careful, as not everything you think works the way you want. So, don’t try to bend the situation. Instead, try to adjust yourself in that manner. Also, never move into something with selfish motives, as it can make your good year into a not-so-good one.\n\n
     Pisces \n\n First things first, be grateful for what you have, Pisces! Even the Pisces yearly horoscope 2023 is urging you to do so. In all aspects of your life, the planetary transits will allow you to spread happiness and attract the same in your life. Work on the motto— one good deed per day! As your horoscope foretells that you have a great high chance of running into pessimism and a dual mind every now and then. When, for once, you thought that the previous year is over and you can take a rest, you saw things coming with more rush and strength. However, Mars transit in 2023 is all set to help you face challenges and mend scenarios for you. But, on the other hand, Rahu will be there too. It could influence your dual nature and lead you into its own tricky ways, away from a fine and pleasant life. But worry not, as, by the end of the year, Pisces natives will be with lessons and learning that would help them figure out their own ways to answer the hindrances life has thrown at them. Also, to make your life happy and easy, stick to something strictly— like a resolution or practice as it will add brownie points to your year ahead.</string>
</resources>
